{"data":[{"question":"Ann usually does the shopping, but I _____ (do) it today as she isn't well.","a":"is doing","b":"are doing","c":"am doing","answer":"3","explain":"- I + am + V-ing.\n- Do -> doing.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Why _____ Ann _____(not wear) her new dress?","a":"aren't \/ wearing","b":"isn't \/ wearing","c":"am not \/ wearing","answer":"2","explain":"- The question form: Wh...+ to be+ S + V-ing...?\n- Wear -> wearing.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"An old man _____ (climb) out of a first floor window!","a":"are climbing","b":"is climbing","c":"am climbing","answer":"2","explain":"- Affirmative: he\/she\/it + is + V-ing.\n- climb -> climbing.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"I can't hear what you _____ (say).","a":"are saying","b":"are saing","c":"is saying","answer":"1","explain":"- You + are + V-ing.\n- Say -> saying.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"The traffic _____ (make) too much noise.","a":"is making","b":"are making","c":"is makeing","answer":"1","explain":"- Affirmative: he\/she\/it + is + V-ing.\n- Make -> making.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"A policeman _____ (try) to move them on.","a":"are tring","b":"is tring","c":"is trying","d":"am trying","answer":"3","explain":"- He\/she\/it + is + V-ing.\n- Try -> trying.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"What _____ you _____(look) at?","a":"are\/looking","b":"is\/looking","c":"am\/looking","answer":"1","explain":"-The question form: Are + you\/we\/they + V-ing...?\n- Look -> looking.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"_____something ______ (happen) in the street?","a":"are\/happening","b":"is\/happening","c":"am\/happening","answer":"2","explain":"- is + something + V-ing.\n- happen -> happening.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"It _____ (rain) very hard. You can't go out yet.","a":"is raining","b":"are raining","c":"am raining","answer":"1","explain":"- Affirmative: he\/she\/it + is.\n- Rain -> raining.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"The airplane _____ (fly) at 2,000 metres.","a":"is flying","b":"is fling","c":"are flying","answer":"1","explain":"- Affirmative: he\/she\/it + is.\n- Fly -> flying.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"2","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"}]}